Contact

8449799894 (Home) lhasobugyal@yahoo.com

www.linkedin.com/in/lhakpawangyal-108a8b49 (LinkedIn) lhakpa.blogspot.com/ (Blog)

Top Skills

aSc TImetable Microsoft Office Microsoft Excel

Languages

English (Full Professional)
Hindi (Limited Working)
Tibetan (Native or Bilingual)

Lhakpa Wangyal

Teacher, Educator, Researcher, Freelancer, Google Trusted Pro Photographer,

Dehradun, Uttarakhand, India

Summary

Attended TCV SCHOOLS (H.P.), India.

Persued B.Sc MCZ(Microbiology, Chemistry and Zoology) and M.Sc Microbiology from ST. Joseph's College(Autonomous), Bangalore, India (2007-2012).

Served as contract Science teacher at SOS TCV GOPALPUR SCHOOL, CHACHAIN, H.P., India (2012-2013).

Completed B.Ed (Life science and physical science) from Lovely Professional University, Phagwara, Punjab, India (2013-2014). Successfully completed M.Phil Microbiology from Lovely Professional University, Phagwara, Punjab, India (2014-2015). Being part of Tibet Corps I was fortunate to serve as an assistant to Education Officers in Department of Education (DoE), CTA, Dharamsala from May 2015 to June 2015.

Later, served as Program Facilitator from June 19, 2015 to March 31, 2016 at Technology Based After School Coaching Center (an undertaking project of DoE, CTA, Dharamsala) located at TCV Selakui, Dehradun.

Started serving as Contract PGT Biology at TCV Selakui, Dehradun since April 1, 2016.

Served as Regular PGT Biology at TCV Selakui, Dehradun since April 1, 2017.

Currently, serving as PGT Biology at Social Baluni Public School, Dehradun

Experience

Social Baluni Public School PGT Biology Cum Senior Co-coordinator April 2019 - November 2022 (3 years 8 months)

Dehradun, Uttarakhand, India

TCV School Selakui, Dehradun

3 years

PGT Biology

April 2016 - March 2019 (3 years)

Dehradun, U.K, India

HOD, Dept. of Science

March 2017 - December 2018 (1 year 10 months)

Avanti Learning Cente, Department of Education, Central Tibetan

Administration

Facilitator/Program manager

June 2015 - March 2016 (10 months)

TCV School Selakui, Dehradun

Tibet Corps

Volunteered as Assistant to Education Officers at Department of

Education (CTA)

May 2015 - June 2015 (2 months)

Dharamshala, India

SOS TCV GOPALPUR SCHOOL, KANGRA, H.P.

Contract science teacher

June 2012 - June 2013 (1 year 1 month)

KANGRA, H.P, INDIA

Taught basic science to secondary school students. Guided inter-school science project competition on 'Global warming'.

Education

Lovely Professional University

M.Phil, Microbiology (2014 - 2015)

Lovely Professional University

B.Ed, Life science and physical Science · (2013 - 2014)

St. Joseph's University

B.Sc, M.Sc, Life Sciences · (June 2007 - May 2012)

Post Graduate and Research Center, ST. Joseph's College of Arts

and Science (Autonomous), Bangalore

M.Sc Microbiology, Microbiology · (2010 - 2012)

ST. Joseph's College of Arts and Science (Autonomous), Bangalore Bachelor of Science (B.Sc.), Microbiology, Chemistry & Zoology · (2007 - 2010)